Approach Archives
Approach Archives
- APPROACH files
  - Correspondence, contributors and authors
    - Kayden, Eugene M. (Box 2)
    - Keith, Joseph Joel (Box 2)
    - Kemp, Lysander (Box 2)
    - Kirkpatrick, Margaret (Box 2)
    - Kizer, Carolyn (Box 2)
    - Kliewer, Warren (Box 2)
    - Kreymborg, Alfred (Box 2)
    - Kristen, Marti (Box 2)
    - Lacey, Paul (Box 2)
    - Laing, Dilys (Alexander), posthumous (Box 2)
    - Lindstrom, Elsie (Box 2)
    - Lane, Frona (Box 2)
    - Langton, Daniel J. (Box 2)
    - Laws, Betty Ann (Box 2)
    - Lawson, Arthur (Box 2)
    - Lax, Robert (Box 2)
    - Lazarus, Arnold (Box 2)
    - Leary, Paris (Box 2)
    - Lehamann, L. Th. (Box 2)
    - Leonard, David (Box 2)
    - Levenson, Christopher (Box 2)
    - Lewis, C. S., several letters not accounted for (Box 2)
    - Lieberman, Laurence (Box 2)
    - Lipton, Lawrence (Box 2)
    - Locklin, Gerald Ivan (Box 2)
    - Logan, John (Box 2)
    - Loescher, Frank and Mildred (Box 2)
    - Luce, Ralph (Box 2)
    - Lyttle, David (Box 2)
    - McAfee, Tom (Box 2)
    - McCall, Virginia (Box 2)
    - McCandless, J. H. (Box 2)
    - McCloskey, Mark (Box 2)
    - McDonald, Frank (Box 2)
    - McGovern, Robert F. (Box 2)
    - McLintock, Kenneth (Box 2)
    - McQuilen, Eleanor A. (Box 2)
    - MacDonald, Dwight (Box 2)
    - MacDonald, Lachlan (Box 2)
    - Madden, David (Box 2)
    - Mager, Don (Box 2)
    - Mager, Gene (Box 2)
    - Marsh, Willard (Box 2)
    - Mary Anthony, S.H.C.J., Mother (Mary Anthony Weinig, Sister) (Box 2)
    - Mary Honora, O.S.F., Sister (Box 2)
    - Mass, Stephen A., publisher, Olympia Press (Box 2)
    - Mauch, James (Box 2)
    - May, J. B. (Box 2)
    - Mayer, Parm (Box 2)
    - Mazzaro, Jerome L. (Box 2)
    - Menamin, Margaret (Box 2)
    - Mendl, Wolf (Box 2)
    - Merton, Thomas (Box 2)
    - Meshorer, Rayna (Silvera) (Box 2)
    - Meudt, Edna (Box 2)
    - Michaelson, L. W. (Box 2)
    - Middleton, Elizabeth H. (Box 2)
    - Millar, Joseph (Box 2)
    - Miller, John N. (Box 2)
    - Miller, Vassar (Box 2)
    - Miller, William F. (Box 2)
    - Mills, Barriss (Box 2)
    - Moffitt, John (Box 2)
    - Mongé, Mildred (Box 2)
    - Moorse, George (Box 2)
    - Morabito, Mary Matosian (Box 2)
    - Moses, W. R. (Box 2)
    - Murphy, Carol; Murphy, Joan (Box 2)
    - Murray, Philip (Box 2)
    - Nelson, C. E. (Box 2)
    - Nemerov, Howard (Box 2)
    - Neville, Helen (Box 2)
    - Nist, John (Box 2)
    - Noll, Bink (Box 2)
    - Nowlan, Alden A. (Box 2)
    - Nuhn, Ferner (Box 2)
    - O'Conner, Flannery (Box 2)
    - Oden, G. C. (Gloria) (Box 2)
    - Oerke, Andrew (Box 2)
    - Offen, Ronald (Box 2)
    - Oliansky, Joel (Box 2)
    - Openlander, Peggy (Box 2)
    - Overmyer, Barbara (Box 2)
    - Patten, Karl (Box 2)
    - Petrie, Paul (Box 2)
    - Pettinella, Dora M. (Box 2)
    - Pharr, Emory C. (Box 3)
    - Philbrick, Charles (Box 3)
    - Pinkney, Dorothy Cowles (Box 3)
    - Platt, David (Box 3)
    - Plotinsky, Melvin (Box 3)
    - Plutzik, Hyam (Box 3)
    - Poots, Tom (Box 3)
    - Powers, Jessica (Sister Miriam of the Holy Spirit) (Box 3)
    - Porges, Michael (Box 3)
    - Proctor, Roy (Box 3)
    - Pustilnik, Jack (Box 3)
    - Rae, George William (Box 3)
    - Rainer, Dachine (Box 3)
    - Ramsey, Paul (Box 3)
    - Randall Mills, Elizabeth (Box 3)
    - Rawlins, Winifred (Box 3)
    - Ready, Richard (Box 3)
    - Reilly, John William (Box 3)
    - Reiter, Thomas (Box 3)
    - Rexroth, Kenneth (Box 3)
    - Ribman, Ronald B. (Box 3)
    - Ridge, (George) Ross (Box 3)
    - Ristau, Harland (Box 3)
    - Ritter, C. H. (Box 3)
    - Robinson, Donald (Box 3)
    - Roseliep, Raymond (Box 3)
    - Rosen, Kenneth F. (Box 3)
    - Rubin, Larry (Box 3)
    - Sainz de Cueto, Francisco (Box 3)
    - Salinger, Herman (Box 3)
    - Samford, T.C. (Box 3)
    - Savage, Catherine (Box 3)
    - Savory, Teo (Mrs. Alan Brilliant) (Box 3)
    - Schevill, James (Box 3)
    - Schwebell, Gertrude O. (Box 3)
    - Shaffer, Blanche (Box 3)
    - Shapiro, Karl (Box 3)
    - Silver, Philip (Box 3)
    - Simon, John Oliver (Box 3)
    - Sister Miriam of the Holy Spirit, See Powers, Jessica
    - Sles, Steven L. (Box 3)
    - Sloan, Jocelyn Macy (Box 3)
    - Smith, Ray (Box 3)
    - Smith, Ruth (Box 3)
    - Smith, William Jay (Box 3)
    - Sneller, Anne G. (Box 3)
    - Stafford, William (Box 3)
    - Stanford, Ann (Box 3)
    - Stapletop, Laurence (Box 3)
    - Steere, Helen (Box 3)
    - Stefanile, Felix (Box 3)
    - Stoop, Noram McLain (Box 3)
    - Stonesifer, Richard J. (Box 3)
    - Stryck, Lucien (Box 3)
    - Sullivan, Lloyd (Box 3)
    - Summer, Hollis (Box 3)
    - Swallow, Alan (Box 3)
    - Sward, Robert (Box 3)
    - Tanda, Joseph (Box 3)
    - Targan, Barry (Box 3)
    - Tassoni, Mrs. Mario, See Domino, Ruth.
    - Thomas, A. F. (Box 3)
    - Thomas, Donald (Box 3)
    - Thorne, Dorothy (Box 3)
    - Thorne, Evelyn (Box 3)
      See also Donovan, Alan.
    - Tinkham, Charles B. (Box 3)
    - Tomlins, Jack E. (Box 3)
    - Tootell, Jack (Box 3)
    - Tonge, Mildred (Box 3)
    - Tongue, Margaret (Box 3)
    - Trudell, Dennis (Box 3)
    - Turco, Lewis (Box 3)
    - Turner, Alberta T. (Box 3)
    - Tyler, Robert L. (Box 3)
    - Van Nouhuys, Dirk (Box 3)
    - Viereck, Peter (Box 3)
    - Votaw, Galja Barish (Box 3)
    - Vroman, Leo (Box 3)
    - Walker, Dorothea (Box 3)
    - Walker, Florence (Box 3)
    - Wallace, Robert (Box 3)
    - Welsh, Chad (Box 3)
    - Welsh, Zach (Box 3)
    - Walters, Colin (Box 3)
    - Wang, David Rafael (Box 3)
    - Washburn, Richard Kirk (Box 3)
    - Watkins, Edward (Box 3)
    - Weeks, Robert Lewis (Box 3)
    - Weinig, Mary Anthony, Sister, See Mary Anthony, S.H.C.J.
    - Wesley, Cecil Cobb (Box 3)
    - Wheatcroft, John (Box 3)
    - Whitbread, Thomas (Box 3)
    - White, Claire Nicolas (Box 3)
    - White, Lourine (Box 3)
    - Wilkins, E.M. (Box 3)
    - Wilkinson, Bethell (Box 3)
    - Wilson, Robley, Jr. (Box 3)
    - Witt, Harold (Box 3)
    - Wolking, Exta Williams (Box 3)
    - Woods, Carl (Box 3)
    - Yelton, Donald O. (Box 3)
    - Young, David P. (Box 3)
    - Young, Mildred (Box 3)
    - Youngblood, Sarah (Box 3)
    - Zachary, Hugh (Box 3)
    - Zahn, Curtis (Box 3)
    - Zander, Williams J. (Box 3)
  - Correspondence, general
    [This subseries includes correspondence with] would-be contributors, general readers, etc. Names in each file are listed under the appropriate letter.
    - A (Box 3)
      Abbott, Lola Creak; Abbott, Warren D.; Abele, Paul; Abrams, Paul D.; Adam, Antoniette; Adams, Phoebe; Adams, Percy; Adler, Carol; Alba, Nanina C.; Albanese, Margaret; Albert, Walter; Alfieri, Benjamin A.; Allen, Jane Ellen; Allinder, Craig; Allison, Sigrid; Altman, Forrest; Altman, H. G.; Amanuddin, Syed; Amelar, Richard; Amsel, N.; Anders, Kaaren; Anderson, Alettre; Anderson, Philip; Andresen, Taddy & Bent; Ankenbrend, F.; Angraves, Hugh Oliver; Arms, Jane (deceased); Armstrong, Richard D.; Ashman, Richard; Atkins, Russell; Ault, Louise; Austin, Alan D.; Avrett, Robert; Ayer, Ethan
    - B (Box 3)
      Bache, Kaye Elizabeth; Bachman, Charles R.; Bail, Jay; Baird, Newton; Baker, Mrs. L.E.; Banke, Loy; Barolini, Helen; Barr, Gayne; Barrese, Pauline N.; Bartlett, Robert; Batie, Jean; Bay, Kenneth D.; Beaver, Wilfred E.; Beisch, Michael J.; Bell, Wm. W.; Bennett, John M.; Bennett, John Z.; Benton, Josephine; Berens, Rita; Bergeron, Lucien A.; Bereday, George; Berges, Ruth; Berman, Bruce A.; Bernard, Kenneth; Berney, Geoffrey; Bilyard, O.E.; Binsfeld, Edmund L.; Birney, Earle; Bissell, David Paul; Black, David Hodosh; Blackwell, Louise; Blake, Richard A., S.J.; Blei, Norbert; Bliss, Alice; Bloomindale, Judith; Bluefarb, Sem; Blum, Etta; Blumenthal, Myron S.; Bodin, Edward; Boggs, W. Arthur; Boros, Ferenc; Boothe, Anna; Borchardt, Georges; Bowen, Robert O.; Bower, Martha Ann; Bracy, Addie Lockridge; Bradley, Anne; Brainard, Franklin; Brashers, Howard C.; Bray, Kathleen; Breedlove, Mildred; Brower, Adam Vincent; Brown, Barbara; Brown, D.; Brown, Joseph Lee; Brownstein, Harvey; Buchanan, Cindi; Buchanan, Pegasus; Bull, Elias B.; Bullock, Marilyn; Bushnell, Scott M.; Butler, James A.; Burelbach, Frederick M., Jr.; Burnam, Tom; Burr, Pamela; Burton, Sheri; Butcher, Grace; Byrne, Joan
    - C (Box 3)
      Cahen, Alfred B.; Callahan, James D.; Campbell, James B.; Canfield, Joan G.; Carlson, Helen; Carogher, Mary E.; Carpenter, Richard C.; Carroll, Donald; Carroll, Sue; Cary, Mary; Casper, Leonard; Castle, Trevor A.; Castleman, Wm. J.; Caltofen-Segura, Rodolpho; Cebulash, Mel; Chamberlin, Myrtle; Chambers, Leland H.; Chappell, Jeannette; Charles of Cheraw; Chase, Dean; Chatfield, Hale; Chatman, Seymour B.; Chickering, Howell, D.Jr; Chrisman, David F.; Christopher, Mary, S.H.C.J., Mother; Cismaru, Alfred; Claire, W. F.; Clark, Kenneth R.; Clark, J. Wesley; Coates, Carrol F.; Cochran, G. Lyne; Coffin, Patricia; Cohen, Marcus Anton; Colabrese, Francis; Cole, David A.; Cole, James; Colvin, Frances Rodney; Colwell, Robert; Contoski, Victor; Cooke, F. B.; Cooke, Robert Crane; Cooley, John R.; Cooper, J. C; Cooper, Kay Anne; Cooper, Ren; Conversi, Leonard; Copeland, Gigi; Corrington, William; Corwin, Walter Joseph; Courtney, Barbara V.; Cowen, Joseph Robert; Craig, Earl; Creighton, John; Crowell, John J.; Crum, V. E.; Cucinotta, Maryanne; Culver, Marjorie Lyle; Currie, Mrs. A. J.; Currier, Raymund
    - D (Box 3)
      Dady, V.R.; Denby, Septimus; Darius, Gregory Denyll; Dash, Robert; dlAuria, Gemma; Davidson, Arthur; Davis, Rik; Davison, John; De Feo, Ronald; DeJong, David C.; DeLaurentis, Louise Budde; de Leevw, Doris Y.; Dell, Wm. C.; Dent, Thomas; de Pledge, Orin C.; de Paola, Daniel; Deutsch, Emil M.; Deutch, Richard; Dike, Ethel H.; Dickey, Helen Gail; Doebler, Bettie Anne; Dokey, Dick; Dorn, Alfred; Downey, Jacqueline; Doyle, Walter; Dragonetti, Mary; Drake, Alfred; Drake, Harold Lee; Dratz, Wm.; Driskell, Leon V.; Ducat, M.; Duke, Phillip S.; Dunetz, Lora; Durrett, Eustace; Dzwonkoski, F. Peter, Jr.
    - E (Box 3)
      Easlic, Annette; Eastman, Margaret; Eaton, Dorothy Burnham; Ebelt, Alfred; Eigner, Larry; Ekern, Raymond; Elcott, E. M.; Elevitch, Y. D.; Ellenbogen, George; Ely, Gladys; Ericksen, Charles; Eshleman, Clayton; Eulert, Don; Evans, R.J.
    - F (Box 3)
      Fackler, Herb; Falleder, Arnold; Faulwell, Dean; Fayne, Louis Lucian; Feathers, Laverne; Feibelman, Marguerite; Feirstein, Frederick; Feld, Brusce; Feldman, Herbert; Fenner, James L.; Figel-Hartman, D.; Filler, Louis; Finch, Donald G.; Fingerman, Chas.; Finch, Donald G.; Fishman, Charles; Fitzsimmons, Thomas; Fitzell, Lincoln; Flanaga, Robert; Flosdorf, James W.; Flynn, Robert John; Fogel, Ruby; Folk, Barbara Nauer; "Forsaking Fathers"; Fowler, Janet; Fox, Chas. A.O.; Fox, Robert R.; Fox-Hutchinson, Mrs.; Franks, Mikhail; French, David C.; Freibert, Stuart; Fried, O.; Fried, Stanley; Friedman, Judith S. & Perlmutter, Ruth; Freidman, Paul; Friedman, S. H.; Frierson, Meade III; Froelich, Quentin; Fuhr, H.D.; Fuller, Larry E.
    - G (Box 3)
      Gallo, Louis; Galt, Toni; Garber, Ethel; Garey, Doris B.; Garrison, Philip; Gatti, Arthur; Gaughan, Dennis N.; Gayet, Patricia; Gecan, Carolyn Elizabeth; Geismar, Maxwell; Georgakas, Dan; George, Richard A.; Gerro, Caron; Gibson, Morgan; Gidley, J. (Mick); Gilkey, Helen L.; Gillespie, Gerald; Gilsdor, Gordon (Rev.); Gladwell, F. E.; Glenn, Nancy S.; Glicksberg, Charles; Goba, Ronald J.; Goldknopf, David; Goldman, Lloyd N.; Goldman, Mark; Göbel, Robert J.; Göller, Carl; Gonzales, Rafael Jesus; Goodger-Hill, Trevor; Gordon, Robert; Gouczy, Janis; Grandin, Ruth T.; Graves, Marlene L.; Gray, Don; Green, David; Green, Louis & Elizabeth; Gregory, Mary; Greaser, Seymour; Griffin, Win. Lloyd; Grilikhes, Alexandra; Grisham, Judy; Grogan, Mary R.; Gronowicz, Antoni; Gunther, Ullrich; Gustafson, Richard
    - H (Box 3)
      Haag, John; Haas, E. M.; Hagedorn, Hermann; Haggerton, Robert J.; Haiduke, Robert; Hall, Claude Raye; Halleckson, Corrette; Halperin, Irving; Halperin, Mark; Hamblen, Abigail Ann; Hamilton, Bruce; Hamm, V. Wayne; Hammer, Jeanne-Ruth; Hannold, Francis H., Jr.; Harley, Peter; Harrold, Wm.; Harsch, Eugene; Hartman, Dorothy; Hasley, Louis; Haynes, Noel E.; Hearn, Winifred J.; Hearst, James; Hedisa (?), Natalie; Heitsch, Leona Mason; Heller, John L.; Helmick, Lucie June; Hendler, Earl; Hendrick, George; Henze, Helen; Herman, Elliott F.; Harriman, Dan; Hess, Harvey; Hill, Hyacinthe; Hills, Kenneth Wm.; Hinchey, James F.; Hinde, Walter D.; Hirschfeld, Mary; Hobson, Warren; Hoey, Lawrence; Hoffberg, Caroline; Hoggins, Carolyn; Holland, William J.; Hollis, Wm.; Hooton, Harry; Horan, Dennis J.; Hosman, David W.; Hotchkiss, Bill; Howe, Charles H.; Howell, Robert M.; Howery, W.H.; Hoyt, Clement; Huey, Jane; Hughes, G.S.M.; Hughes, Lillian; Hull, Anthony; Hull, William (not APPROACH contributor); Hume, Martha H.; M. Humiliata, I.H.M., Sister; Hunt, Evelyn Tooley; Hunt, Wm.; Hunter, Harry A.; Hunter, Paul; Hunting, Constance; Hyman, Sally
    - I (Box 3)
      Ignatowski, David; Inez, Colette; Inman, Will; Ipavec, Julia; Ireson, J.C.; Iver, Elsa; Isbell, Harold
    - J (Box 3)
      Jackinson, Alex; Jacobs, Gerald; Jacobs, Lee; Jacobs, M.G.; Jacobs, R. L.; Jacobsen, Ethel W.; Jaffe, Dan; Jaffe, Marie B.; Jamieson, Wm. A.; Janes, Kelly; Janse, Donald L.; Jehle, Herbert; Jewell, Rhoda de Long; Johnson, Edith Warner; Johnson, Geoffrey; Johnson, Louis; Johnson, Margaret Lee; Johnson, Maynard; Johnson, Rick B.; Johnson, Robert K.; Jonas, Ann; Jones, David; Jones, Gerard; Jones, Ilse Nesbitt; Jones, Peter; Jones, Robert C.; Jones, Thos. L.; Jones, Virginia A.
    - K (Box 3)
      Kaldegg, Gustav; Kalugin, David; Kamenetsky, Christa; Kaminsky, Stuart M.; Kane, Robert L.; Kann, Emma E.; Kaplan, Elaine Toby; Kaowith, Vicki; Kasberg, K.G.; Katz, Menie; Kaufmann, C.W. Jr; Kaufmann, Donald L.; Keatts, Margee E.; Keen, Michael Elliot; Kelly, Robert; Kelly, J. Wallace; Kempf, Joseph H.; Kempher, Ruth; Kenedy, R.C.; Kenedy, Robert; Kenison, Gloria; Kessler, Jascha; Kessler, Milton; Keyser, George; Keyser, Wilfred; Khall, Sheloh; Khamadi, Miriam; Kiernan, Edith; Kilpatrick, Martha; King, June M.; Kingston, Marion Sherwood; Kipp, Dave; Kirk, Norman Andrew; Kirkner, Phoebe S.; Kirkpatrick, C. W.; Kitaif, Theodore; Kitchen, Anna; Knight, Kenneth (an APPROACH editor); Knoll, Molly; Knox, Hugh; Koppenhauser, Allen J.; Koretz, Gene; Kramer, Larry; Kretz, Thomas, S.J.; Kriebel, John; Krotz, Friedrich Wahelm; Kuenkel, Wolfgang; Kyros, Nicollette
    - L (Box 3)
      Lambert, Ronald; Lancaster, R. D.; Lanzi, Elizabeth; Lape, Fred; la Rochelle, Don; Larsen, G.; Larsen, Richard B.; LaSelle, Eunice Pond; Laurita, Raymond E.; LeGrande, W. Ames II; Lems, Carol Silver; Lengyel, T. C.; Lensing, George, Jr.; Leroy, Richard; LePage, Portia E.; Lery, D. A.; Lewis, J.M.; Lewisohn, James; Lextrom, Arvid F.; Lieberman, Morris; Lima, Robert Francis; Lincoln, Maryland; Lind, Laura; Lindeman, Jack; Lipton, Helen; Lisker, Roy; Livengood, Roy; Locke, Jan; Lockridge, Addie; Long, Clayton; Long, Pierre (Marjorie Peters); Lonidier, Lynn; Lord, Gigi; Lorden, Peter; Love, Jean O.; Lowery, Wm. G.; Lovett, James; Lund, Mary Graham; Luster, Helen; Lyman-Martineau, Richard; Lyons, Barbara
    - Mc (Box 3)
      McAleer, John J.; McAvoy, Francie; McCandless, Esther L.; McCann, Sharon Quigley; McCord, Howard; McDonnell, Thomas P.; McElroy, Jerry X., S. J.; McGinn, Arthur J.; McKay, Cherry; McLaughlin, Wm.; McLeod, J.; McMorries, M. L.; McMullen, R.; McNamee, Datid W.; McNamee, Edward; McQuilken, Frank
    - Mac-My (Box 3)
      MacArthur, Gloria; MacCreary, Marjorie; Macrow, Brenda G.; Makler Gallery; MacLeod, Iris Jean; Major, Clarence; Malaschak, Dolores; Malone, Marvin; Manly, Morse; Mann, Herbert; Mansell, Darrel, Jr.; Margolis, Wm. J.; Mariah, Paul; Marsden, Roy; Marshall, John; Martinek, Joseph; Martz, Wm. J.; Mary Emmanuel, Sister, CSJ; Mary Hild, USA, Sister; Masters, Hilary; Masterson, Daniel E.; Mathews, Richard; Matthews, Wm.; Matzke, Connie; Maxon, Gloria; Meyer, Sharon E.; Mayhall, Jane; Meehan, John J., Jr.; Meeker, Mary; Mendenhall, Dorothy; Merrell, Ronald Y.; Merritt, Frank W.; Messier, Barbara; Metz, Jerry; Meyer, Emil; Meyers, Thomas; Michelman, Dorothea; Miller, Brown; Miller, Drew; Miller, James; Miller, Marcia Muth; Miller, Richard Wallace; Millet, Martha; Mills, Ralph; Mitchell, Juanita; Mode, Michael D.; Modrall, Donald F.; Moffitt, Helen Reed; Mohn, Earl R.; Montgomery, Marion; Mooney, Stephen; Moore, John H.; Moot, Edmund Northrup; Morgan, Robert; Morin, Edward; Morrell, Roger M.; Morris, Mary Louise; Morris, C.H.; Morrison, Lillian; Morse, Jonathan; Moses, Aloe; Moulton, Priscilla; Moyer, Daniel Jr.; Muck, Gordon; Mullins, Helene; Munro, Kathryn; Munro, Ronn; Myers, J. Wm.; Myers, Walter.
    - N (Box 3)
      Napora, Paul Edward; Nash, Edmee B.; Navasky, V.; Nealon, Eleanor; Neave, Adam; Neaville, Viena K.; Neely, E.J.; Negelspach, Gerard; Neuberger, Hans; Newberry, Wm.; Newlin, Vivian H.; Newman, Louis; Newman, Montgomery; Newman, Paul B.; Newton, Christopher; Neylon, James; Nicholson, John; Nierenberg, Edwin; Noble, Wm. J.; Noller, Rose; Northnagel, E. W.; Nowlin, Edna V.
    - O (Box 3)
      Oates, J. C.; O Broin, Padraig; O'Brien, Wm. P.; O'Conner, L.O.; O'Connor, Mary; O'Connor, Philip F.; Oetaria, Andjar; O'Higgins, Michael C.O.; Oleson, Helmer O.; O'Neal, Valera F.; Opalov, Leonard; Orlen, Steven; Osborn, Rebecca
    - P (Box 3)
      Packard, Wm.; Packardson, A. A.; Pakenham, J.; Paladin, Thomas; Palmer, Candida; Palmer, David; Palmer, Margot; Panolt, Jerry; Papayianis, Milton; Paquette, Donald J.; Pack, Jacquelyn; Park, Leora Voss; Peacock, K.C.; Pebworth, Ted-Larry; Peck, Richard E.; Peirce, Rosamond F.; Pelletier, Gaston F.; Pennock, Betty; Percikow, Henri; Perez, Genara Jesse; Perkins, Albert C.; Perkins, Walter W.; Perlman, Jess; Peters, Anne; Petri, Lori; Petty, W. H.; Phillips, Robert S.; Plett [?], Eric; Phillips, T. J.; Pierce, W. W., Jr.; Pilibosian, Helene; Pilate, Gaston; Pinto, Biagio; Pinsker, Sanford; Piser, Harold Palmer; Pitchford, Kenneth; Pobog-Malinowski, Tomasz; Polinsky, Ethel; Porter, Jenny Lind; Porter, Margaret A.; Porter, Norman; Postan, Linda; Powell, Clarence Alva; Powell, Nova (Mrs.); Pratt, Laurence; Preston, John; Prill, Douglas; Pritchard, Sheila; Puechner, Ray; Putname, Mary Ann
    - R (Box 4)
      Raab, Lawrence; Ragg, Louis G.; Ralph, George; Ramsey, Jarold W.; Ranz, J.J.; Ratcliffe, Eric; Ratliff, K; Reddin, Myra; Rebert, M. Charles; Rees, Alun; Reib, John Dan; Reich, Don; Reinstein, Herman; Remak, Henry H.H.; Renken, Alecto; Richardson, Dorothy Lee; Richardson, Nels; Rick, Velma Richardson; Ridley, Gustave; Riemann, Robert G.; Riscalla, Louise Mead; Rizzo, Fred; Roberts, Bob; Roberts, Percival R., III; Robin, Ralph; Robinson, Forrest; Robinson, R. L.; Roby, Juliet; Rock, E.S.; Rohr, Anne; Rose, Phyllis; Root, Wm. Pitt; Rosberg, Rose; Rosenblatt, Herta; Rosenhouse, Archie; Ross, Allison; Ross, Dan; Rubin, Maude; R (Ruppert), Christopher; Ruskin, Eugene D.; Rutherford, Vada; Rutsala, Vern
    - S (Box 4)
      Sable, Sylvia; Sajkovic, Miriam; Salisbury, Ralph; Salley, Ernestine M.; Sanger, Jan; Sanders, Stark; Sarfrazahmad, Mian; Sargent, S.M.; Saunders, Sally; Sayres, Wm.; Schaefer, Rockwell R.; Scherer, Bob, Jr.; Scheurich, James; Schimmelfennig, Victor; Scheberlein, Marion; Schmidgall, Benny; Schor, Sandra; Schramm, Irene; Schreiber, Roy F.; Schub, Phyllis; Schul, Bill D.; Schwartz, Barry N.; Schweige, Eleanore; Scott, Evelyn; Scott, Herbert; Scroggs, Schiller; Seaburg, Carl; Seibert, R.E.; Seigfred, Shirley; Sellin, Eric; Semenovich, Joseph; Shames, Ann; Shea, Robert J.; Shefner, Evelyn; Shelton, Richard; Shepard, David L.; Sherman, Bobbi; Sherman, Wm. David; Sherwin, Judith Johnson; Shetter, Vim. Z.; Shipps, Sara Beth; Shoemaker, Brant; Shoemaker, Jack; Silas, Barbara S.; Silver, Marian (Arthur); Simmons, Andrew; Simmons, J. Edgar; Simon, Howard; Sims, P.T.; Singer, James; Skardon, Philip; Sleicher, Sally; Smail, Annette K.; Smith, Harry; Smith, Howard E., Jr.; Smith, Marjorie B.; Smith, R.E.; Smith, Wm. I.; Smith, Wayne Leroy; Smythe, Daniel W.; Snodgrass, Betty; Snyder, Maryhelen; Snyder, Richard; Snyder, Wayne Wm.; Solovay, Jacob C.; Songhurst, Robert; Sonya, Kathie; Soule, Daniel; Sparks, Robert W.; Speer, Laurel; Spielberg, Peter; Spinelli, Jerry; Stabley, Rhodes; Stantor, Robert, Jr.; Staplin, Florence; Stark, Kendall; Steele, Robert S.; Steinman, D.B.; Stern, Harold; Sternlicht, Sanford; Steuart, Mary Douglas; Stewart, Dolores; Stewart, Vincent A., Jr.; Stiver, Mary Weedon; Stock, Robert; Stoddard, Hope; Stoffel, Liz; Stokes, Terry; Stoloff, Carolyn; Stone, Gayle Adams; Stone, John M.; StorM, Hester G.; Stout, Robert Joe; Strange, Wm.; Strauss, Erika; Stromberg, Wm.; Sublette, Margaret; Sullivan, Immelda M.; Sullivan, Nancy; Sutter, Ellen; Swaim, Alice MacKenzie
    - T (Box 4)
      Taft, Tom; Tanier, Maurice; Tavani, Robert Hartwell; Taylor, Henry S.; Taylor, Kora; Teitelman, Ed; Temple, Wick; Terrell, Jim; Terzian, P. Henry; Tharp, Roland; Thomas, P.D.; Thompson, Mary McCullough; Thorpe, Peter; Tibbets, Y.; Tibbs, Ben; Tifft, Ellen; Tolnay, Thomas; Toosey, Catherine Brewster; Travis, Helen Muriel; Trowbridge, Clinton W.; Trueblood, Elton; Trumbo, Dalton; Trunzo, Russell; Tucker, Agnes C.; Tucker, Edward; Turnbull, Phyllis; Turner, Beulah A.; Turner, Myron; Turner, Neysa
    - U (Box 4)
      Ulrich, Wm.; Unterecker, John
    - V (Box 4)
      Vale, W.; van de Pol, Michele; VanDerVoort, Richrd L.; Vaudrin, Bill; Vaughan, Robert; Vaughon, Thos.; Vinsel, Art; Vogel, Albert W.; Vogel, Jo; Vonalt, Larry P.; Vorres, Ian
    - W (Box 4)
      Wade, John Stevens; Wall, Mary B.; Walker, Don D.; Walker, Ralph W., II; Walters, Jay A.; Wardell, Jack; Warshaw, Nancy; Watkins, Hilda K.; Watkins, Thos. C.; Watson, David Newall; Weathers, Winston; Weaver, James E.; Webb, Joyce W.; Weber, R.; Weigel, Henrietta; Wein, Louis; Weiss, Betty; Weiss, Hymne; Weiss, Irving J.; Weisslitz, E.F.; Westcott, Roger W.; Whatley, Mary; White, Edgar J.; White, James P.; White, Wm. M; Whitney, J.D.; Whitman, Wm.; Wiackley, Mildred; Wilem, David M.; Willard, N.; Williams, Dorothy M.; Williams, Gerald; Williams, Jenna; Williams, Leonard; Williams, Melvin G.; Williams, Miller; Wilson, Ingeborg; Wilson, Richard; Winsor, Philip; Witherspoon, Maude; Wolf, Robert; Wood, Emma S.; Wood, Judy; Woodson, Weldon D.; Worth, Ellis; Wright, Dave; Wright, Jay; Wright, Joseph C.; Wright, Waldo Carlton; Wu, Jack; Wyndhambell, Sherlock; Winters, Anne
    - Y (Box 4)
      Yezzetti, E. C.; Yellen, Samuel; Yenawine, Emily; Yglesias, Kenneth; Young, Arthur H.; Young, Elisabeth; Young, Virginia Brady; Yuzon, Amado M.
    - Z (Box 4)
      Zabriskie, George; Zamurrad, Malik M.; Zelenka, Robert S.; Zinnan, M. E.; Zittau, Herbert; Zivkovic, Peter D.; Zleh, Koiran
  - Miscellaneous
    [This subseries includes] APPROACH advertising campaigns, the make-up of the unpublished APPROACH anthology, editorial decisions, correspondence about the 1964, 1965, 1966 Poetry Awards, etc.
    - APPROACH advertising rates (Box 4)
    - Appreciations from APPROACH readers (Box 4)
    - ALMA (Assn of Literary Magazines of America) (Box 4)
    - APPROACH ads in other magazines (Box 4)
    - APPROACH Anthology, mounted pages, Sections I, II and III, 3 folders (Box 4)
    - APPROACH Anthology, carbons (Box 4)
    - APPROACH articles, unfinished (Box 4)
    - APPROACH editors' publications (Box 4)
    - APPROACH inventory (Box 4)
    - APPROACH listings in indices and writers' journals, etc. (Box 4)
    - APPROACH Poetry Prize for 1963 (Box 4)
    - APPROACH Anthology, records of decisions (Box 4)
    - Books sent in for review (Box 4)
    - Book and press announcements (Box 4)
    - Katherine & Elizabeth Bragdon Poetry Awards for 1965 (Box 4)
    - Katherine & Elizabeth Bragdon Poetry Awards for 1966, 2 folders (Box 4)